MARK J. LINDSKOG

LinkedIn • Github • Portfolio • lindskoamarki@amail.com • (567) 203-9473 • Columbus, OH 43204

SUMMARY ——————————————————————

Recently completed the Google Cybersecurity certificate with previous experience as a manual tester with coding experience, having previously completed a 6-month Full Stack Web Development Bootcamp through Ohio State University. I want to continue to learn and grow my skill set, as well as use my professional communication abilities to make an impact on teams.

TECHNICAL SKILLS -

Languages: Python, Javascript ES6+, CSS3, HTML5, SQL, NoSQL, Linux

Applications: GitHub, MongoDB, MySQL, Heroku, TestRail, Jira, Insomnia, Postman

Tools: Express, Node, Query, Handlebars, React, Bootstrap, Foundation, MUI, Charles Proxy

PROJECTS -

Scriber | https://github.com/mjlindskog/scriber | https://powerful-shore-38656.herokuapp.com/

Summary: App for writers and note takers with text to speech functionality

Role: Front end author, text-to-speech implementer

Tools: Express, Node, JavaScript, MUI, React, Apollo GraphQL

EXPERIENCE -

MoneyPigeon, Columbus, OH | August 2022 - August 2023

Software QA Engineer

- Reviewing user interfaces for conformity and functionality by applying QA tools and methodologies
- Designing test cases in TestRail and providing test execution based on analysis of business requirements and specifications
- Configuring virtual devices applying BrowserStack, Android Studio and Xcode
- Identifying and reporting issues in Jira and monitoring defect status
- Designing data validation through a database with SQL-queries
- Performing API testing, creating collections and running different calls using Postman
- Collaborating with product manager and developers to meet the requirement and ensure a quality product

NuGrowth Solutions, Columbus, OH | February 2020 - May 2021

Dedicated Tactic Group Campaign Representative

- Representative for multiple accounts in the market daily, tripling number of impressions in the market
- ► Create interest and generate pipeline development within a 90-day client cycle for each account

Inside Sales Representative

- Create over 250 impressions into the market each week through phone and email
- Product expert responsible for qualifying prospects and running through demonstrations

EDUCATION & CERTIFICATIONS -

Coursera | Google Cybersecurity Certificate | 2023

Project Management Institute | Disciplined Agile and Scrum Master | 2022

Ohio State University | Coding Web Development Certificate | 2021

Ohio University - Athens, OH | Bachelor of Arts - History | 2015 - 2019